speedify.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Speedify

_Effective Date: May  28, 2014_  
_Updated May 11, 2018_

##  TL;DR: We DO NOT log what you do or what sites you visit through the Speedify service.  

Connectify, Inc. (“Connectify,” “we,” “us”) respects your privacy and as such we strive to collect the minimal amount of information necessary to operate our service. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information we collect through our website at speedify.com (the “Site”) and the Speedify service, and how we use this information to provide outstanding value to you.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you should contact us at [privacy@speedify.com](mailto:privacy@speedify.com)

## How do you Protect the Privacy of my Speedify Sessions?

 **We do not log the IP addresses of websites that you visit or the contents of data sent or received through the Service.**

We do not log the IP addresses of websites that you visit or the contents of data sent or received through the Service. Certain protocols, such as “torrents” or Tor, may be blocked on some or all servers.

Communication to our backend servers and databases are encrypted with SSL, and firewalled to restrict access to only authorized servers. Furthermore access to customer data is limited only to employees who require access in the delivery of the service.

## What Personal Information We Collect

###### Contact information:

We receive contact information from customers who buy our products through the Fastspring store. This includes name, phone number, email address, personal address, and company name. Customers who create an account on our Speedify service may provide an email address.

###### Homepage Access Logs:

Our servers log access to our homepage, including IP address, page accessed, browser type and operating system.

###### Device Information:

Our services log access information about the client device, including IP address, and unique device identifiers. Some of the information collected varies depending on the device used and its settings and in accordance with device consent policies. A unique identifier from your hardware device may be used to generate a token to identify the session with the server to provide service without providing an email address.

###### Location Information:

Speedify collects approximate location from your device and from 3rd parties, for example using a GPS or IP-based approximation. This information is collected according to the consent policy on your device.

###### Cookies:

To read more about our cookie policy, click [here.](https://www.speedify.com/cookie-policy)

###### Support Requests:

We may request more information when you contact our support. As appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name and email address.

###### Speedify Server Access Logs:

The following user specific logging data are captured by the servers: (1) the time and network location from which an initial Speedify connection was made; (2) the amount of data transferred, (3) approximate location, and (4) the duration of the Speedify connection. This information allows Connectify to troubleshoot issues, and improve performance.

## How Does Connectify Use This Information?

###### To provide services:

  * For the authentication of users and devices
  * Communication about your account, subscription status, or license

###### To improve our services:

  * Measuring server infrastructure load 
  * Determine where to increase server capacity
  * Connecting you to the fastest available servers

###### To send emails and other communications:

  * Including advertising new features, software updates, or new products
  * Marketing messages, such as new promotions or company stories
  * We provide an opt-out for communications unnecessary for the delivery of our services.

###### To respond to support requests:

  * Support staff may request identifying information to verify your account status.

## Does Connectify Disclose Information to Outside Parties?

We will not sell or rent your personal information to other companies. Additionally, we cannot disclose information about the services, websites, or applications you utilize while connected to our Services as we do not store this information.

Except as described below, we will not disclose your personal information to outside parties.

  * Third Party Service Providers – See list of trusted third parties below for more detail
  * Legal Compliance – We do not log what you do through our servers, so we do not have any such information to provide to law enforcement or anyone else. Outside of this, we, like all companies, need to comply with the legal process including court orders and other requests from law enforcement and regulatory authorities.
  * Assignment – We reserve the right to transfer personal information to a new entity or third party as part of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of some or all of our assets, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). We will notify you via email or prominent notice on our web site if the third party’s or new entity’s treatment of personal information will materially differ from the treatment described in this Privacy Policy.

## Third Party Service Providers  

###### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the Service, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s privacy policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

###### Raygun

This Service uses Raygun for error and exception tracking. In the event you encounter an error while using the Service a message will be sent to Raygun with information pertaining to the error. Information collected will include your IP address, and email address (if provided). If you do not wish to share this information, you may turn it off from inside the application by going to the “Help Menu”, selecting “Privacy”, and then turning off the “Crash Reports” setting.

###### Fabric

In order to provide continuous improvement, Speedify uses the crash reporting service Fabric (owned by Google). By agreeing with this privacy policy you also agree with the privacy policy of Fabric. For more information about the data collected by the Fabric service, please refer to the Fabric privacy policy found [here.](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us)

## Additional Rights

Individuals located in certain countries, including the European Economic Area, have certain statutory rights in relation to their personal data. Subject to any exemptions provided by law, you may have the right to request access to Information, as well as to seek to update, delete or correct this Information.

To request access, deletion or correction of your personal information, email us at [privacy@speedify.com](mailto:privacy@speedify.com)

## Protecting the Privacy of Children

Our Services are not intended for use by children under the age of eighteen (18) and are not directed at such children. Please do not register at Connectify if you are under the age of eighteen (18). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If you have information about a child using our service, please contact [privacy@speedify.com](mailto:privacy@speedify.com)

## Transferring Personal Data from the EU to the US

Connectify has its headquarters in the United States. Information we collect from you will be processed in the United States. The United States has not sought nor received a finding of “adequacy” from the European Union under Article 45 of the GDPR. Connectify relies on derogations for specific situations as set forth in Article 49 of the GDPR. In particular, Connectify collects and transfers to the U.S. personal data only: with your consent; to perform a contract with you; or to fulfill a compelling legitimate interest of Connectify in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and freedoms. Connectify endeavors to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of your personal data and to use it only consistent with your relationship with Connectify and the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Connectify also minimizes the risk to your rights and freedoms by not collecting or storing sensitive information about you.

## Data Storage and Retention

Your personal data is stored by Connectify on its servers, and on the servers of the cloud-based database management services Connectify engages, which may be located in the United States. Connectify retains data for the duration of the customer’s or member’s business relationship with Connectify. For more information on where and how long your personal data is stored, and for more information on your rights of erasure and portability, please contact the Connectify’s data protection officer at [privacy@speedify.com](mailto:privacy@speedify.com)

## Data Protection Authority

Subject to applicable law, you also have the right to (i) restrict Connectify’s use of your personal data and (ii) lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority or the Irish Data Protection Commissioner, which Connectify has designated as its lead supervisory authority in the European Union. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area and believe we maintain your Personal Data within the scope of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our lead supervisory authority:

Irish Data Protection Commissioner  
Office of the Data Protection Commissioner  
Canal House, Station Road, Portarlington, Co. Laois, R32 AP23, Ireland  
Phone +353 57 868 4757  
Fax: +353 57 868 4757  
Email: [info@dataprotection.ie](mailto:info@dataprotection.ie)

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If this policy is updated, we will post changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on the Site.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact Connectify:  
For Privacy Questions:  

For Other Questions:  

By Mail:  
1429 Walnut St  
Suite 201  
Philadelphia, PA 19102  
USA
